Aazan Khan **Pathan**

Web Developer

My self Aazan Khan Pathan, in 2022, I earned a bachelor's degree in **Commerce** from the University of Sindh Jamshoro, right after I joined several non-profit organizations, voluntarily. In my expertise, I'm best at computer skills, Communication Skills, Report Writing skills.



aazank517@gmail.com

03118679523

Hyderabad, Pakistan

github.com/aazankp

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Verge Systems

02/2024 - Present

Qasimabad, Hyderabad

Web Developer Intern

YAS Solution

11/2022 - 02/2023

Latifabad Hyderabad

MIS Assistant / Data Entry Officer

Management & Development Foundation -MDF

11/2022 - 06/2023

Qasimabad Hyderabad

Web Developer Intern

Verge Systems

08/2023 - 01/2024

Qasimabad Hyderabad

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce

University of Sindh Jamshoro

01/2019 - 05/2022

2nd Class

DAE Computer Information Technology -CIT

Government College of Technology Hyderabad

01/2019 - 12/2021

A Grade

Web Development & Designing

Faith College of Information & Technology, Hyderabad

03/2022 - 06/2022

SKILLS

3rd Party Integration

LANGUAGES

Englsih

Full Professional Proficiency

Sindhi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Urdu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Back End Developer